

### CUSTOMER SERVICE EXPERT

Contact Info



267-838-0772



Glenside, PA 19038



Starr.Robbins@yahoo.com



www.linkedin.com/in/starrrobbins

# STARR ROBBINS

#### AREAS OF EXPERTISE

I've worked with various types of administrative projects and love communicating with people. I have consistently hit goals in call-center sales and service environments. I also have a nack for deescalating angry customers while maintaining a positive attitude. I am proficient in Microsoft office (Word, PowerPoint, and Excel)!

#### EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

#### LAUNCH CODE (PRESENT)

LC101 FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT BOOTCAMP

#### NORTHERN VIRGINIA COMMUNITY COLLEGE

COMMUNICATION (ASSOCIATE DEGREE)

#### WIDENER UNIVERSITY (2011-2021)

COMMUNICATIONS

#### PROFESSIONAL HISTORY

#### TEACHING ASSISTANT

ANICIPLUS TECH | JANUARY 2020 - PRESENT

- Assists teachers with lesson preparation by getting materials ready and setting up equipment.
- Revises lesson material with students individually or in small groups.
- Collaborates with lead teachers to recognize issues students are facing and recommend solutions
- Setup and maintain Google Classroom

#### ADMINISTRATIVE ASSISTANT \*TEMP\*

WELLS FARGO (GPS) | AUGUST 2019 - DECEMBER 2019

- In charge of various calendars, scheduling appointments, and various office tasks
- Uses software such as Outlook, Microsoft Word, PowerPoint, and Excel.
- Edits small grammar errors and do meticulous data entry.

## STARR ROBBINS

## CUSTOMER SERVICE EXPERT

Contact Info



267-838-0772



Glenside, PA 19038



Starr.Robbinseyahoo.com



www.linkedin.com/in/starrrobbins

## PROFESSIONAL HISTORY (CONTINUED)

#### ACCOUNTING ADMIN SUPPORT

QUARLES, INC | AUGUST 2018 - JUNE 2019

- Maintains department record keeping and filing to ensure data and documentation integrity
- Verify previous months Bills of Lading against Monthly Report, obtain missing Bills of Lading
- Sort and File verified previous months Bills of Lading
- Print and enter manual invoices in Telapoint Accurately complete orders into system
- Work closely with other functional teams to ensure data quality and consistency
- Assist in data import/entry and invoice processing
- Assist in card production, packaging and mailing

#### AQUATICS ASSISTANT MANAGER

LIFETIME ATHLETIC | APRIL 2017 - AUGUST 2018

- Ensures Aquatics Team Members provide a safe, friendly and fun environment for members
- Reviews potential new team members and Conducts initial phone interviews,
- Makes hiring, promotion, disciplinary, and termination recommendations to upper management
- Markets and promotes aquatics programs and activities in the club to increase participation
- Assists in calculating revenue and budgetary guidelines for aquatics programs
- Completes and documents daily inspections to ensure pool area cleanliness and safety
- Assists in facilitating lifeguard training on pool safety and rescue techniques
- Trains team members through shadowing, orientation, direction and feedback
- Assists in planning, offering, and registering members for group and private swim lessons
- Assists in organizing, communicating, promoting, administering, and supervising of all department and swim programming

#### CUSTOMER SERVICE REPRESENTATIVE \*TEMP\*

NUTRISYSTEM, INC. | JANUARY 2017 - APRIL 2017

#### CUSTOMER SERVICE REPRESENTATIVE \*TEMP\*

UNITEDHEALTH GROUP | JULY 2016 - JANUARY 2017

#### PATIENT CARE SPECIALIST

PHILIDOR RX SERVICES | APRIL 2015 - JANUARY 2016 \*COMPANY CLOSED\*